coloradomoms.com 2005-04-07

# Colorado Moms :: Meet Colorado Moms and Dads in our Online Parenting Community

**Privacy Policy** **Colorado Moms** recognizes the privacy concerns of visitors to our web site on the Internet ([www.coloradomoms.com](http://www.coloradomoms.com/)) and the importance of protecting the privacy of personally identifiable information collected from them. As a general policy, no personal information, such as a visitor's name, address, e-mail address, or telephone number, is automatically collected on our website. Such information is collected only when knowingly and voluntarily submitted. We maintain reasonable and appropriate safeguards to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of such information in our possession.   
**  
Collection and Use of Personal Information**  
**Colorado Moms** collects and uses personal information for the purpose for which it was submitted. In addition, **Colorado Moms** may use personal information you submit to this site for research, advertising and marketing purposes, including sending you information about products and services that we think you will be interested in. You can instruct **Colorado Moms** not to use your personal information for a different purpose by contacting us.

**IP Addresses**  
**Colorado Moms** collects non-personal user information (for example, IP addresses). An IP address is a number given to a user by a Web Server. Examples of information provided by an IP address include service provider, type of browser and type of system used. **Colorado Moms** may use this information to make its site better and more responsive to the needs of the user. This non-personal information is not shared with third parties for marketing, advertising or research purposes. An IP address is not used to obtain personal information about a user.

**Revision Date:** This document was revised on January 20, 2005.
